YYeTs人人影视字幕组出品
更多原创字幕翻译 请登陆www.YYeTs.net
■
时间轴： YY
后期： 孤帆  字幕总监： YY
■
翻译： 取子小Q  vero  一块二  蔷爆
后期： 孤帆  字幕总监： YY
■
校对： YY    后期： 孤帆  字幕总监： YY
老爸老妈浪漫史
第六季  第七集
因此  就因一个建筑学上的勘漏
And so, due to one architectural oversight,
造成了1906年托莱多大桥大难
the Toledo Bridge Disaster of 1906
致使75人丧生
claimed the lives of 75 people.
真讨厌讲到兴头上让我下课
Now, I hate to stop while I'm on a roll,
不过万圣节快乐  你们这帮小疯子
but happy Halloween, ya crazies!
喂  莫斯比兄
Hey, Professor Brosby,
待会儿一起去喝啤酒吧
You gonna come get beers with us later?
不了  还有事呢
Nah, I got a thing.
你们几个小鬼玩得开心点哦
But you kids have fun trick or treating.
你的糖果真让我们开心
This is a treat.
你最酷了  莫斯比教授
You're the coolest, Professor Mosby.
没有啦  人家是热狗来滴
Well, hot dog.
很疼吧
Did it hurt?
什么
What?
用手术刀把那孩子的手
Getting that kid's nose
从马屁股上割下来
surgically removed from your ass.
她不是在拍我马屁  她是真心的
It's not her nose that's in my ass, Lily, it's her heart.
我的学生都很爱我
My class loves me
我真的给他们留下了很好的印象
I-I'm really making an impression on those guys.
我还是想给她们留下点好印象
I'd like to make impression on those guys.
哥们  我爱死办公室的万圣节派对了
Man, I love the office Halloween party.
比办公室圣诞节派对淫荡多了
It is so much sluttier than the office Christmas party.
不过论变态程度  那可比不上疯狂大吐槽的总统纪念日
Though not as freaky as the office President's Day Rave.
或是嗑完药穿着睡衣  就来庆祝的犹太树木新年日
or the office Tu B'Shvat Pajama Jammy-Jam.
嗨  大伙好  老大好
Hey, guys. Hey, Boss.
嗨  兰迪  来杯啤酒吗
Hey, Randy. Uh, you want a beer?
不了  谢谢你  我有自己酿的
Oh, no, thank you. I brew my own.
不是我自夸  我的榛子比尔森啤酒
At the risk of bragging, my Hazelnut Pilsner
在威霍肯养老院烧烤雪蛤大会
won fourth prize at the Weehawken Retirement Home Clam Bake
和"轮椅生活"的野餐中  赢得四项大奖哦
and Wheelchair Maintenance Picnic.
我看不到有任何值得自夸的地方
I wouldn't consider any part of that bragging.
对了  我刚想起来  你们的朋友
Hey, it just occurred to me, is your friend--
叫什么来的  格宾  弗拉宾
what's her name? Garbin, Flabin...
-罗宾吗  -罗宾  对  就是那个
- Robin? - Robin. That's it, yeah.
她今晚来吗  我也不是很关心啦
Is she coming tonight? Oh, not that I really care.
罗宾去了另一个派对
Robin has another party to go to.
靠  人算不如天算
No! Damn it!
我先闪了
I'm leaving.
不过她待会可能过来转转
But she might stop by later.
我想我还是再玩一会儿好了
I guess I can hang out a little longer.
对了  有没有人要去看万圣节游行啊
So, anyone going to see the Halloween parade?
我们当时超爱纽约万圣节游行
Oh, we were big fans of New York's annual Halloween parade.
我说的不是在格林威治村举办的那个万圣之夜
I don't mean the one that takes place Halloween night in the Village.
而是11月1日早上
I mean the one that takes place the morning of November 1st--
万圣节羞耻之行年鉴
the Annual Post Halloween Walk of Shame Parade.
看看他们
Look at them
肮脏淫秽地滥交一晚后  狼狈不堪地走回家
heading home after their dirty, filthy hookups.
看这B[蜜蜂]  累得都走不动了
Looks like that bee got busy.
看来法国女佣滚了一个晚上的床单
Looks like that French maid didn't turn down somebody's bed.
看  老汉推车式让宝嘉康蒂的膝盖伤得够厉害的
Oh, looks like Pocahontas has a couple of wounded knees.
[宝嘉康蒂:《风中奇缘》女主角]
-喂  马修  -别太过火了
- Come on, Marshall. - That's a line.
-没有啦  我只是因为...  -我们懂
- No, it's because of the... - We get it.
还有什么能比这更欢乐
Does it get any better than this?
那个  有的
Uh, yes.
亮点来了
Yes, it does.
逮个正着
Crap.
看  与陌生人销魂一夜的俏护士南丁格尔
There she is-- Florence Night-In-Bed-With-A-Stranger.
快说  谁有幸做你的病人呢
So, who's the lucky patient?
我不想提这事儿
I don't want to talk about it.
拜托  别告诉我你又跟
Please tell me you're not hooking up
你的联合主播搞在一起了
with one of your co-anchors again.
我的联合主播是个女的
My co-anchor's a woman.
拜托  求你告诉我  你们搞在一起了
Please tell me you are hooking up with one of your co-anchors again.
罗宾一直坚信
Robin had always believed
成功之道
that the key to success
在于能力  努力与专业的态度
was intelligence, hard work and professionalism.
而她新任的联合主播贝基  却有另一套处世哲学
Her new co-anchor Becky had a different philosophy.
大游艇  小游艇  大小游艇
Boats! Boats! Boats!
这是一场汉普顿远郊游艇秀
It's the Far Hampton Boat Show!
大游艇  小游艇  大小游艇
Boats! Boats! Boats!
记住  五六七三天
Remember 5th, 6th and 7th
汉普顿远郊市中心
at the Farhampton Civic Center.
大游艇  小游艇  大小游艇
Boats! Boats! Boats!
一起来吧
Come on down.
大小通吃
B-B-B-Boats!
你拍广告了
You did a commercial?
为啥不能拍
Why not?
你是个新闻工作者
You're a journalist!
你就没想过要被尊敬吗
Don't you want to be taken seriously?
没  我是美少女
No. I'm cute.
好吧  你要真觉得这样
Okay, well, if you really think
有利于你树立形象的话
this is going to help your image.
嗨  贝基
Hi, Becky.
大游艇  小游艇  大小游艇
Boats, boats, boats!
罗宾  来搭把手
Robin, a little help here?
可怜的罗宾
Aw... Oh... Robin,
你没必要担心自己不受欢迎的
You gotta not worry so much about being liked.
站着说话不腰疼
Oh, easy for you to say.
大家对老师都是又敬又爱的
Everybody loves you at your job.
作为老师 确实是这样没错
That was true of my teaching job.
但我也曾为巨人国家银行设计新总部大楼
But I was also designing the new headquarters for Goliath National Bank
那时...
and well...
泰德・莫斯比  我们讨厌你
Ted Mosby, we don't like you!
你拆掉一栋如此美丽的建筑
What do you have to say for yourself,
就为了个什么破总部大楼
tearing down a beautiful, old building
你对此有什么想说的吗
just to put up a stupid band headquarters?
想想啊
Hmm...
爱
Boo...
咋
freakin'...
咋地
hoo.
爱咋咋地  就完了吗
Boo freakin' hoo? That's it?
阿卡迪亚酒店
The Arcadian
堪称建筑奇葩
is an architecturally significant...
建筑奇葩个头啊
Architecturally significant?!
苏伊  你真的很美
Zoey, you're very pretty.
你的头发真好闻
Your hair smells great.
这叫洗发水  或许你也该洗个头了
Shampoo. You should try it sometime.
你懂个屁建筑学啊
You don't know the first thing about architecture.
准备  泰德・莫斯比出现
Key Ted Mosby's car.
接着说
Go on.
我是个教授好不好
I'm a professor, okay?
我在全国最好的大学之一里教建筑学
I teach this stuff at one of the best colleges in the country.
我才不像你混得连个工作都没有
I don't go down to your place of non-employment
也不用教训你  告诉你
and lecture you about how your little protest
你那小小游行完全是浪费时间
is a misguided waste of time,
不过  哎呦喂  我刚教训完
except whoops, I just did.
欧耶  气死你
Ha-burn.
-太好了  鸡蛋来了  -那我先撤了
- Oh, good, the eggs are here. - Well, I should head up.
巨人国家银行一点也不受欢迎
No, GNB was not popular.
所以他们才会每年做足表面功夫
That's why every year they produced a feel-good video
去拍一些光鲜的广告
to improve the bank's image.
是什么让巨人国家银行
What makes Goliath National Bank
如此与众不同呢
different from other big banks?
巨人银行  用心关怀
Here at GNB, we care.
我关心我们赖以生存的地球
I care about our precious Earth.
我关心老弱
I care about old people.
我关心高回报的海上投资项目
I care about high-yield offshore investments.
小拖船也是
And so does Tugboat here.
对不对啊  小拖船
Isn't that right, Tugboat? Yeah.
好了  在我让你滚出去之前
Okay, get that camera out of my face
别再拿镜头对着我了
before I flip you like a cheese omelet.
你只需要说一句
All you have to do is say
"我关心让梦想照进现实"
"I care about making dreams come true."
首先  这句台词听起来很下贱
First of all, that line makes me sound like a hooker
说出来会让我觉得自己是贱人
and saying it makes me feel like a hooker, so.
大家都录过了
Everyone is in this video.
兰迪也上了镜
Randy's in the video.
我不是自夸  但重拍的29次中
I don't want to brag, but in 29 takes,
我只吐了三回
I only threw up thrice.
等等  兰迪  你把赫曼森公司的合同
Wait. Randy, did you send the Hermanson
送到市中心去了吗
contracts downtown?
送去了
I did.
我送去市中心了
I sent them downtown.
你干嘛要说谎
Why are you saying it like that?
市中心的办公室从没收到过
They never arrived at the downtown office.
这个
They...
咱们说的是同一件事吧
Well, just to make sure we're on the same page,
"送到市中心"的意思
is "send them downtown"
不是销毁文件的委婉说法吗
not an expression for shredding a document?
你把文件销毁了
You shredded them?!
是啊  我把它们送去市中心了
Yeah. I sent them downtown.
往下塞进碎纸机
You know, down into the shredder.
市中心一词的字面意思是  下城
把纸张倒过来
You-you feed the paper
喂进机器里
in a downwards fashion,
这个暗语就是这么来的
so that's where the expression comes from.
这不是什么暗语
That's not an expression!
从来就没有过暗语
That has never been an expression!
这事交给我吧
Okay, I can fix this.
这个项目我很熟
I am all over this project.
我要说
I'll say this:
那家伙是个祸害
There is no quit in that guy.
你该解雇他
You should fire him.
行了  就这句话
Okay, that, that right there.
你这态度  正是我不愿上镜头的原因
That attitude is exactly why I won't be in your video.
因为巨人银行毫无关怀可言
Because GNB doesn't care.
他们解雇人  已经是家常便饭了
They hand out pink slips like they're hors d'oevres.
就在上周  我正跟亚瑟说话
Just last week, I was talking to Arthur...
你系着条绿领带
Oh, whoa, you're wearing a green tie now.
绿领带是我系的
I'm wearing a green tie.
巨人银行不把人当人看
GNB treats people like they're disposable,
我可不会与他们为伍
and I will not be a part of that.
马修・埃里克森是不会解雇职员
Marshall Eriksen does not fire people,
现阶段不会
period.
通知你们一下
Uh, just want you to know,
这个新项目  进展顺利
we are making good progress on this new project.
你们接着聊
Oh, you gentlemen keep talking,
我来接电话
I will answer that.
马修・埃里克森办公室
Marshall Eriksen's office.
好的  我可以帮你查
Yeah, I can get that for you.
稍等
Just a second.
银行  GNB中的"B"指的是银行
Uh... bank. The "B" stands for bank.
好了  妈妈  晚上见
Okay, Mother, I'll see you tonight.
糟了  我去给一团糟先生拿张纸巾
Oh, yikes. I'd better get Mr. Messy a napkin.
我说现阶段
Period.
跟我说  你到底跟谁上床了
Just tell me who you slept with!
莉莉  我不想聊这个  好吗
Lily, I don't want to get into it, okay?
我知道了  是我们认识的人
Aha, it's someone we know.
如果是我们都不认识的陌生人
If it was some ding dong we didn't know,
你只要说出他的名字就行了
you'd just give me his name.
好吧  他叫比尔・佩伯
Fine. It's Bill Pepper.
比尔・佩伯
Bill Pepper?
对啊
Mm-hmm.
这真巧了  桌上正好有
Kind of a coincidence there happens
一份账单和一罐辣椒粉
to be a bill and a pepper shaker here on the table.
Bill有账单的意思  Pepper有辣椒的意思
你和比尔是不是还和一个叫福柯纸巾的人玩3P了
Any chance you and Bill had a three-way with Fork Napkin?
被识破了
Oh...
果然是我们认识的人
It's someone we know!
我想你们都读过了
So, I'm assuming you all read the chapters
希腊复兴时期建筑的相关章节了
on the Greek Revival architecture.
有什么问题吗
Any questions?
我有  你晚上能安心睡觉吗
Yes. How do you sleep at night?
你在这儿干嘛
What are you doing here?
我最近突然觉得
It was recently made clear to me
我对建筑一无所知
that I don't know the first thing about architecture,
所以我就来了
so here I am.
很好  那开始上课吧
Very well, then, let's get started.
有哪些属于希腊复兴时期的建筑呢
Some examples of Greek Revival architecture...
我知道  我知道
Ooh! Ooh!
阿卡迪亚大楼  是希腊复兴建筑吗
Is The Arcadian Greek Revival?
不是
No.
阿卡迪亚大楼是什么
What's The Arcadian?
是莫斯比教授打算拆毁的
Oh, it's just this beautiful, old building
一座非常古老而美丽的建筑
that Professor Mosby wants to tear down.
什么  不会的
What?! No,
莫斯比教授对古建筑充满热爱
Professor Mosby loves old buildings.
他不会这么做的  对吧  泰德
He wouldn't do that. Right, Ted?
回到希腊复兴时期...
Getting back to Greek Revival...
我被他们鄙视了
I lost them.
你太没任教的经验了
Look, you're new at teaching.
在我幼儿园班里
In my kindergarten class,
有一大堆不听话的学生
I have had plenty of troublesome students.
比如强尼・马列
Like Johnny Marley...
强尼
Johnny?
Johnny!
他和他的毛绒小马  成天不得消停
He and that little stuffed horsey raised all kinds of hell.
但我有个简单的法子制服他们
But I have a simple method for shutting down troublemakers.
你们还记得  总停在外面的
You know that '98 Taurus that's
那辆98款福特金牛车吧
always parked outside?
警报器异常恼人的那辆
The one with the really annoying alarm?
那声音我们太熟悉了
We're familiar with it.
每当班里有像强尼那样的孩子捣乱时
Well, when a kid like Johnny acts up in my class...
立刻就能让他们闭嘴
Shuts them right up.
莉莉  我的学生是成年人
Lily, my students are adults,
我要以成年人的方式对待他们
and I treat them that way.
我只要给他们带些糖果
I'll just give them more candy
再放上一张混音唱片
and make them a mix CD.
问题就解决了
Problem solved.
宝贝  怎么了
Oh, baby, what's wrong?
我干了件坏事
Something bad happened.
兰迪  你有没有看见...
Randy, hey, have you seen the...
你问之前让我先说
Before you get to that,
之前我在做的那个项目
regarding the earlier project I was working on...
大功告成
Voil?
那是赫曼森公司的合同吗
That's the Hermanson contract?
是要赫曼森公司的
The Hermanson contract?
倒霉  这是费尔伯特公司的
Oh, man, this is the Filbert contract.
-该死  -不要
- Damn it! - No...
你刚才要问什么
Anyway, what's your thing?
我需要费尔伯特公司的合同
I need the Filbert contract!
不是吧
No!!
这样  我会尽我所能
Well, I'll do what I can.
但凭我的经验而言
But in my experience,
粉碎两次  就无可还原了
twice shredded is fairly permanent.
抱歉  兰迪  但是
Sorry, Randy, but...
这样下去不是办法
this just isn't working out.
马修终于开苞了
Marshall popped his cherry!
好了  马修  你得承认那个人确实是个灾难
Come on, Marshall, you have to admit, the guy was a disaster.
他给公司蒙羞
I mean, it reflected badly on the company.
他是个耻辱
He was an embarrassment.
一个巨大的耻辱
A huge embarrassment.
你和兰迪上床了
You slept with Randy!
什么
What?!
太简单了 我亲爱的特布罗特生 [模仿福尔摩斯对华生说话]
Why, it's elementary, my dear Scherbatson.
你的同事因为一条白痴的广告
Your co-host is getting super-popular
变得超受欢迎
because of her stupid commercial,
大游艇  小游艇  大小游艇
"Boats! Boats! Boats!"
你在我们走了之后  来到GNB的办公室派对
So, when you arrived at the GNB party after we left,
你心情低落  酩酊大醉
you were feeling vulnerable and drunk.
在那个人并不多的会议室里
Then, from across the not-so-crowded conference room,
你们俩  对上眼了
your eyes met.
而且众所周知
And as we all remember...
兰迪有一个特殊的情况
Randy has a unique condition.
你鼻血流的跟水龙头一样
Yeah, your nose is bleeding like a faucet.
天啊  只要我一勃起就这样
Oh, God, this happens every time I get an erection.
真是抱歉
I am so sorry.
那
That's...
就是事实
...exactly what happened.
看见没  马修
See, Marshall,
如果说被炒鱿鱼是执行死刑
if getting fired is an execution,
那至少他在临死前享受了最后的晚餐
at least the guy had a last meal.
我向你保证
I promise you,
明天你就会好的
tomorrow you'll feel a lot better.
兰迪  怎么了
Randy, hey, what's going on?
我只是想说我并不生气
I just wanted to say no hard feelings.
谢谢
Thank you.
那你现在要去哪
So where you headed now?
下去啦
Downtown.
不要
No!!
没事的  宝贝
It's okay, baby.
一点都不好
It wasn't okay.
第二天早晨
So the next morning...
亚瑟  我来这是因为我犯了一个错误
Arthur, I'm here because I made a mistake.
我昨天炒了兰迪
I fired Randy yesterday.
那确实是个错误
That was a mistake.
你一年前就该把他炒了
You should have fired him a year ago.
不  先生  这是这家公司的问题所在
No, sir, that is what's wrong with this company.
我们怎么能一边高喊"巨人银行  用心关怀"
How can we say "GNB Cares,"
一边转身这样对待别人呢
and then turn around and treat someone like that?
当然  他确实犯了一些错误
I mean, sure, he made a few mistakes,
但是人人都会犯错
but everybody makes mistakes.
就像小拖船一样
Like, like Tugboat here.
我打赌它肯定也犯过错
Aw. I bet you he's made some mistakes.
但你也没有放弃小拖船  不是吗
And you didn't fire Tugboat, did you?
没  我把它阉了之后  现在好多了
No, I got him fixed, and he calmed down.
就是这样  其实也不尽然
Exactly, kind of.
兰迪需要的不是炒鱿鱼
Randy doesn't need to be fired.
他需要的是修整
He needs to be fixed.
马修  在这里我们干很多坏事  但是我
Marshall, we do some pretty bad things around here, but I...
不  先生  我希望当人们犯错时
No, sir, I'm saying instead of getting rid of someone
我们应该帮助他们  而不是把他们开除
when they screw up, we should... we should help them.
我们应该培育他们
We should nurture them.
我连续三天每小时
I changed the ice pack on his crotch
给它换一次胯下的冰敷袋
every hour for three days.
埃里克森  如果你想返聘兰迪  我支持你
Wow, Eriksen, if you want to un-fire Randy, I support you,
因为来到这里  说出你刚刚的那番话
because to come in here and say what you just said,
你和小拖船确实有很大的不同
well, you've got a couple things that Tugboat doesn't.
同学们  摇滚教授这张自制CD真的很棒
Guys, Prof Rock is a really good mix, okay?
一段纽约历史将被摧毁
A piece of New York history is being torn down,
而你却说"爱咋咋地"
and all you could say was "Boo freakin' hoo"?
爱咋
Boo... freakin'...
或许是我在一次玩脚球沙包的时候
I may have mentioned our conversation
跟他们小提了一下我们的对话
over a session of hacky sack.
我没来沙包小组的那天
The one day I miss the sack circle,
你们让她进来了
you guys sub her in?
你为什么会没来
Why'd you miss?
忙着拆毁自由女神像吗
Too busy tearing down the Statue of Liberty?
不是  我正忙着退还你们都很喜欢的热狗服
No. I was returning a hot dog costume that you all enjoyed.
他们开始攻击我
They were all turning against me,
所以我想  管他呢
so I figured, what the hell.
管用吗
And did it work?
超级管用
Like gangbusters.
我们又是好兄弟了
We're buddies again.
下课以后  我们又踢了一会儿沙包
After class, we hacked a little sack
伴随着我摇滚教授那张CD的强劲音乐
to the thumpin' strains of my Prof Rock CD.
是的  他们没人听过小妖精乐队的《B-side》专辑
And no, none of them had heard the Pixies B-side.
[the Pixies 1986年成立于波士顿  解散于1993年]
就是因为他们都不知道小妖精这个乐队
Actually, none of them had heard of the Pixies.
我才可以光明正大把《 B-side》这张专辑偷来用
Or a B-side.
你们好
Hey, guys.
我见过那个笑容
Uh-oh. I know that smile.
莉莉  你要挺住
Lily, there's no easy way to say this.
马修死了
Marshall's dead.
兰迪杀了他
Randy murdered him.
不对  我知道兰迪为什么会笑
No. I know why Randy is smiling.
是因为罗宾
You're smiling because of Robin.
罗宾  就像我洗澡的时候幻想她那样吗
Robin? Like how I think about her when I'm in the shower?
我在吃饭呢  老兄
I'm trying to eat here, buddy.
不是  因为你万圣节那天和她上床了
No. Because you slept with her on Halloween.
什么  没有啊
What? No.
我回了家  洗完澡就睡觉了
I went home, had a shower an-and went to bed.
你没和她上床吗
You didn't sleep with her?
没有
No.
哪怕是在洗澡的时候
Even in the shower,
我们最多也就是抱抱
the farthest we ever get is hugging.
那你笑什么
So why are you smiling?
我来告诉你们
I'll tell you why.
不能再这样下去了
This just isn't working out.
真好  我又要被炒鱿鱼了
I'm fired. Great.
就跟以前的商场蜡烛事件一样  历史重演了
This is the candle kiosk at the mall all over again.
等一等
Wait a minute.
我能拿到一笔赔偿金
I can get a severance check.
只要我不把它放粉碎机里撕毁了
If I don't shred it,
我就可以用那笔钱开一家啤酒厂
I can use that money to start my own brewery.
想象会有一瓶印上我名字的啤酒
Imagine a beer with my name on it.
兰迪・温尿  这是你人生中最美好的一天
Randy Wharmpiss, this is the best day of your life.
多亏了那笔赔偿金
Thanks to that severance check,
明年的这个时候  你们将会品尝到
this time next year, you'll all be enjoying
一杯泡沫丰富的温尿啤酒
a frothy mug of Wharmpiss.
兰迪  特大喜讯
Randy, great news!
你没有被解雇
You're not fired!
搞毛啊
No...!
早上好  各位
Good morning, everybody...
我的学生呢
Where's my class?
你好  教授
Hello, Professor.
完胜
Ha-boom.
我把你的工作争取回来了  兰迪
I got you your job back, Randy.
我以为你会很高兴
I thought that you'd be happy.
但是我跟这里格格不入
But I don't belong here.
我生来就是个酿酒师  我是啤酒花大师
I'm born to be a brewer! A... a hopsmeister!
那就辞职啊  没人阻止你
Well, then quit. No one's stopping you.
我不能  我需要赔偿金
I-I can't. I need my severance check.
真不好意思  兰迪  这是诈骗
Well, I'm sorry Randy, but that's called fraud.
这不是诈骗
It's not fraud.
我只是想你炒了我  然后得到大笔赔偿金
I'm just asking you to get me a lot of money to not work here
并且不告诉任何人
and not tell anyone about it.
即使我炒了你  我还是要向亚瑟汇报
Even if I wanted to fire you, after my talk with Arthur...
得了吧  亚瑟不会记住这点小事的
Oh, come on, Arthur can't remember that.
马修  昨天的谈话真是让人记忆深刻
Marshall, what a memorable talk we had yesterday.
兰迪  我谨代表巨人银行的每一位员工
Randy, on behalf of everyone at GNB,
无论是坐牢还是出狱的
both in and out of prison,
我们对此事深感抱歉
we're sorry.
而且我要向你保证
And I want to assure you
你再也不会被开除了
you will never be fired again.
你会在这一直工作直到你死为止
You're going to work here until you die, huh?
绿色领带
Green tie?
有品位
Nice choice.
谢谢  非常夺目
Thanks. It brings out my eyes.
没错  我真想夺走你的目
Yeah. I'll bring out your eyes.
兰迪  我很抱歉
Listen, Randy, I'm sorry,
但是我曾经打破了我的道德准则
but I broke my own moral code once
我很有负罪感
and I felt evil.
我不会让巨人银行改变我
I will not let GNB change me.
我永远也不会开除任何一个人
I will never fire anyone again ever.
那我们走着瞧
Oh, we'll see about that.
管他的  我对准了
Anyhoo, while I got you--
笑一个
big smile.
"我们关心让梦想照进现实"
"We care about making dreams come true,"
三  二
in three, two...
不
No!
你这是干嘛
What are you doing?
你不爽我吗
Oh, are you unhappy with my performance?
我想我被解雇了
Well, I guess I'm fired, then.
我最好上交我的ID卡
I'd better turn in my I.D.
不  实际上
No, it's actually,
真高兴你把我桌上的杂物弄走
um, nice having some of this clutter off my desk.
谢谢了  兰迪
So thank you, Randy.
还有更精彩的
And there's more.
我不知道我拍这个干嘛
I don't know what I'm going to use this for,
但这真是好镜头
but it's great stuff.
现在我被解雇了吗
Now am I fired?
我早就想彻底打扫那些文件柜
I've been meaning to clean out that file cabinet for ages.
当我是透明的
I'm not even here.
兰迪  还有咖啡
Randy, the coffee.
好吧
Oh! Okay.
Okay.
真是谢谢你了  兰迪
Thank you, Randy.
我一直想减少咖啡因的摄入量
I've been meaning to cut back on my caffeine.
拿这个试试  使劲用力泼
Here, try this, but really go for it.
记住  这家伙毁了你的人生
Remember, this guy ruined your life.
这就是我需要的提神饮料
That's just the pick-me-up I needed.
说到提神  第一个镜头能再来一遍吗
Speaking of pickups, can we try the first one again?
你好
Hello.
那招不管用了  他们讨厌我
It didn't work. They hate me.
怎么才能让他们再喜欢我
How do I get them to like me again?
你不需要
You don't.
泰德  你是他们的老师
Ted, you're their teacher.
唯一喜欢老师的那种人
The only people that like their teachers...
我喜欢我的老师
I like my teachers.
是白痴
...are dorks.
除了你  迈尔斯
Except for you, Miles.
泰德  你只需要学习接受他们的恨意
Ted, you just have to learn to embrace their hatred.
因为在恨意的背后  是恐惧
Because behind that hatred lies fear.
你能利用恐惧
And you can use that fear,
就像我对约翰・尼马利一样
like I did with Johnny Marley.
难道那个故事不止这么简单
Was there more to that story?
有一点
A little bit.
莉莉  你简直是神经病
Lily, you're a psychopath.
是有点
A little bit.
哇  熊猫真好看
Oh, a panda!
我考虑了莉莉的建议
I thought about Lily's advice.
我认为利用恐惧  值得一试
And I figured fear was worth a try.
莫斯比教授
Well, Professor Mosby,
你想对我们说些什么吗
is there anything you want to say to us?
明天不在教室的人  成绩是F
Anyone not in class tomorrow gets an "F."
你那样说的
You said that?
专业上来说  是他们成绩不完整
Well, technically, they'd get an incomplete,
但我觉得"F"对他们来说是一个不错的警钟
but I thought "F" had a nice, scary ring to it.
-对吧  -没错
- Right?  - Yeah.
罗宾  你和谁睡了
Robin, who'd you sleep with?
我告诉你了  兰迪
I told you-- Randy.
他就是个永动机
He was a machine.
又睁眼说瞎话呢  罗宾
Where's the poop, Robin?
好吧  我没和任何人睡
Fine. I didn't sleep with anyone.
问题是  自从贝基做了那个广告
The thing is, ever since Becky did that commercial,
每个同事都喜欢她
everyone at work loves her.
所以万圣节的后一天  我在拍广告
So, the day after Halloween, I was in a commercial.
什么  你为什么不告诉我们
What... Why didn't you tell us?
膀胱有问题  是非常尴尬
Bladder trouble-- it's embarrassing,
非常不自在  而且无一人能避免
it's uncomfortable,and it can affect anyone.
我现在就要去厕所
I'm going to the bathroom right now.
安全舒适的成人纸尿裤
Neat and discreet adult diapers
大人小孩都适用
for anyone.
说
Say...
我等不及想看了
Wow! I can't wait to see it.
但愿你永远看不到
Well, hopefully you never will.
他们说可能不会用它
They said that they might not even use it.
他们用了七年
It ran for seven years.
好吧  你赢了
Okay, you win.
或许破坏你的办公室是错的
Maybe trashing your office was a mistake.
只不过  在我能记事的时候
It's just, uh, as long as I can remember,
酿造啤酒就是我的梦想
making beer has been my dream.
温尿牌
Wharmpiss?
我知道对已经完成梦想的人来说 这主意很愚蠢
I know it sounds dump to someone who's already achieved his dream
大公司里面的一流律师
big-time lawyer at a huge corporation.
你认为在这工作是我的梦想
You think working here is my dream?
当然
Of course.
总之   我会把这清理干净
Anyways, I'll clean this stuff up.
叫人把死松鼠从你办公桌上弄走
Have someone get that dead squirrel out of your desk.
兰迪
Randy.
非常好喝
This is delicious.
你被解雇了
You're fired.
孩子们  隔天早上
Kids, the next morning--
我的课堂上出勤率达到史上最高值
my class had the highest attendance, ever.
过了没多久
And not long after that,
兰迪用他的赔偿金开了一个小型啤酒厂
Randy used his severance money to start a little brewery.
现在你在美国任何酒吧  都买到温尿牌啤酒
Now you can have a Wharmpiss at every bar in America.
全都因为
And all because...
我关心让梦想照进现实
I care about making dreams come true.
你得到你想要的了吧
You got what you need?
拍摄完工
Yep. That's a wrap.